thefranchisemall.com 2005-04-12

# Alltheweb: Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

**This privacy statement was last updated on 09/20/2004.**

AllTheWeb.ca is owned and operated by 1589771 Ontario, Inc., an Ontario corporation. We have created this privacy statement in order to disclose its information gathering and dissemination practices for the website located at [www.alltheweb.ca](http://www.alltheweb.ca/). 

Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know: 

  1. The personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the website. 
  2. The organization collecting the information. 
  3. The manner in which the information is used. 
  4. The parties with whom the information may be shared. 
  5. The choices available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under AllTheWeb.ca's control. 
  7. The manner in which you may access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to AllTheWeb.ca by contacting us through our Contact Page or by writing to us at the following address: 

Attn: AllTheWeb.ca Privacy  
1589771 Ontario, Inc.  
405 King Street North Suite 111  
Waterloo, Ontario Ontario

**Client Information Collection and Use**

AllTheWeb.ca is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. AllTheWeb.ca collects information from its Advertisers and Traffic Partners (the "Clients") as well as from Internet users who initiate keyword searches from sites operated by our Traffic Partners (the "Internet Users") at several different points on our website.

**Client Registration**

In order to become an Advertiser and Traffic Partner, a user must first complete our online registration form. During registration, a user is required to provide their contact information (including name, email address, physical address and telephone number). Part of the registration process also requires prospective Traffic Partners to provide their Social Security Number or Federal Tax I.D. Number in order to receive payments from AllTheWeb.ca as part of our Traffic Partner Program. Part of the registration process also requires Advertisers to provide their credit card information (including their credit card number, billing address and CVV2 security number). We use this information to process and authorize payments that are initiated by Advertisers using our online payment platform.

**Regular Communication with Clients**

As part of our process in serving our Clients, we routinely communicate via email, mail or telephone with our Clients. In addition to our initial welcome letter, our Clients receive account activity reports, low balance warnings, funding confirmation emails, site and service announcement updates, and other information relating to the management of their AllTheWeb.ca accounts. Clients also receive emails directly from a member of our team offering optimization or other services designed to assist Clients. Out of respect for the privacy of our Clients, we will honor every request not receive these types of communications.

**Newsletter to Clients**

Our Clients receive a regular newsletter from us. If a Client wishes to unsubscribe to our newsletters, he or she may do so by unsubscribing directly from our newsletter. We do not sell, share, or rent our newsletter email list to any third party.

**Client Surveys**

From time-to-time, we may request information from our Clients by email or through an online survey. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the Client therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any of the requested information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), demographic information (such as zip code, age and income level), information about other forms of online advertising that is used by the Client, information related to the Client's experience as a AllTheWeb.ca Advertiser or Traffic Partner, and information related to the business of the Client. Information that we gather in this way is intended to get important feedback from our Clients with the purpose of improving the quality of our services. We may share the information that we collect, but no information will be attributed to any individual Client without written authorization from the Client. 

**Advertiser Credit Card Information**

We request credit card information from our Advertisers. As part of this process, an advertiser must provide contact information (including name, email address, telephone number and billing address), their credit card number, expiration date and CVV2 number. This information is stored in our system, with the exception of the CVV2 number, which is only used to authorize the credit card the first time it is used. The information is used to fulfill the Advertiser's requests to fund their online advertising accounts. The billing address is used to authorize the charge to their credit card; the email address and telephone number will be used if it is necessary to contact the Advertiser regarding the processing a request or to otherwise address billing issues.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our website. However, Traffic Partners and Advertisers who disable cookies will be limited in some areas of our site. 

**Collection of Data from Internet Users**

AllTheWeb.ca does not collect Internet User identity or contact information from Internet Users' visits to AllTheWeb.ca's website or to any of its Traffic Partner websites. For each visitor to a AllTheWeb.ca website or to any of its Traffic Partner websites, the visitor's computer reaches us via a particular Internet Protocol (the "IP") address. AllTheWeb.ca's servers automatically collect this IP address.

An Internet User's browser sets cookies (when enabled) that contain small amounts of data on the Internet User's computer after a visit to any website. Cookies assist AllTheWeb.ca in tracking Internet Users' activities beginning from a Traffic Partner's website through to Advertiser's site listing that the Internet User clicked on from AllTheWeb.ca's website or through the Traffic Partner's site. If the Internet User conducts other searches and clicks on the Traffic Partner's website, AllTheWeb.ca is able to continue to track the Internet User's activities on the Traffic Partner's website and compensate the Traffic Partner that referred the Internet User. The information contained in the cookies do not provide AllTheWeb.ca with any personally identifiable information about the Internet User.

The function of these cookies is to provide AllTheWeb.ca with information solely for the purpose of paying Traffic Partners commissions when an Internet User clicks on an Advertiser's search results listing. No information is obtained from the Internet User or Internet User's computer to generate the unique identifying number of the Internet User. AllTheWeb.ca's servers automatically generate the unique number. None of AllTheWeb.ca's cookies are used to perform "User Profiling." If a Web site using AllTheWeb.ca's tracking technology were to provide any personally identifying information to AllTheWeb.ca beyond name and/or email address, AllTheWeb.ca would discard that information immediately.

**Sharing of Client Information**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our Traffic Partners and Advertisers from time-to-time. The information that we may share is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual user. We use an outside credit card processing company to process the credit cards of our Clients. This company has advised us that they do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any purpose other than processing transactions on our behalf. In the future, we may partner with other parties to provide other specific services related to the services that we provide for our Clients. In such instances, we may be required to share personally identifiable information about our Traffic Partners and Advertisers that is necessary for the third party service provider to provide these services. These parties will not be allowed to use personally identifiable information related to our Clients except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links to Other Sites**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be advised that AllTheWeb.ca is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites that link to or from AllTheWeb.ca. We encourage our Clients to be aware that privacy policies may differ when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website and through Traffic Partner websites.

**Security**

AllTheWeb.ca takes many precautions to protect our Clients' information. When Clients submit sensitive information via the website, information is protected both online and offline. Sensitive information (such as credit card numbers and email addresses) is encrypted using SSL. While on a secure page, such as all of the pages within our account management interface, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are not on a secure page. To learn more about SSL, [click here](http://developer.netscape.com/tech/security/ssl/howitworks.html).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect user information offline. All information related to our Clients is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific function (for example, our Account Managers) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All our databases are accessible only through password-protected interfaces. 

Furthermore, all employees are routinely advised of our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure the integrity of our Clients' personal information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage, at a third party hosting facility.

**Corrections/Updating Personal Information**

If our Clients' personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data. This can be done within the "Admin" section of our Account Management Interface or by contacting our Advertiser Services Team through our Contact Page or by telephone at **(519) 489-4444**.

www.alltheweb.ca

We have the right to change our privacy policy at any time. If we do so, we will post those changes in this section of our website so that our Clients are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose such information.

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify Clients by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you require further information regarding the above policies, or would like to request that you cease receiving any particular form of communication from us, please contact us through our Contact Page or by telephone at (519) 489-4444.
